<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Brian G. Richards</title>
    <link>http://briangrichards.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Brian G. Richards</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://briangrichards.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AMLCville and DataCamp Courses</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/amlcville-and-datacamp-courses/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 May 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/amlcville-and-datacamp-courses/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been busy over the last few months working on my data science skills. Starting around the beginning of the year, I started working on the DataCamp career track for Data Science using Python. I recently completed it and really enjoyed my time working on it. I feel like the courses have given me enough knowledge that I can do a little bit of work in Python and get started on learning more independently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Announcing Simply Approximate</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/announcing-simply-approximate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/announcing-simply-approximate/</guid>
      <description>After several years of trying to get it off the ground, I have finally launched my blog site. It is called Simply Approximate and will be the home of my rambling thoughts on Data Science, Physics, and any other thing that happens to interest me. So if you want to see what I am working on, check it out! A permanent link to the blog will be available in the sidebar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/graduation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/graduation/</guid>
      <description>Another belated announcement! Back in July I defended my dissertation and in August I officially graduated. For any who are interested in the work that I have done, my dissertation is freely available from the University of Virginia library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transitioning to Blogdown</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/transitioning-to-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/transitioning-to-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>I have felt for a while that this site needs a refresh. Previously, I had built it using Jekyll on a Windows machine. I’ve found that Jekyll was a pain to use in a Windows environment and that kept me from updating this site regularly. Fortunately, a few months ago I attended a RStudio webinar given by Yihui Xie on his new blogdown package.
Welcome to the new site created in blogdown!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Publications</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/new-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/new-publications/</guid>
      <description>I am pleased to (belatedly) announce a pair of publications!
The first is work that I did examining the line shapes of dipole-dipole interactions in a cold Rydberg gas.
The second is work done with Tao Zhou on the absence of collective decay in a cold Rydberg gas.
Both of these papers can be found at the links to the APS journal websites above.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/about/</guid>
      <description>I am a data scientist, Physics Ph.D., and R enthusiast interested in the intersection between data science techniques and how these techniques can be used to solve interesting and complex problems. I am particularly interested in developing data acquisition, processing, storage, and analysis pipelines to enable more researchers to easily access complex topics. As part of my Ph.D. research I developed a package for R called starkr that is currently available on GitHub.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CV and Resume</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/cv/</guid>
      <description>Brian Richards Resume</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/resume/</guid>
      <description>Brian G. Richardshttps://www.linkedin.com/in/briangrichards/
SummarySkilled at communicating complex topics using both technical and non-technical language.Developed R package to solve Physics problems (available on GitHub).A diligent worker at developing workflows for data acquisition, cleaning, analysis, and visualization.Dedicated to continued learning and skill development.SkillsProgramming Languages: R, LabVIEW, Markdown, LaTeX, Git, SQL, Python
R Package Experience: ggplot2, dplyr, tidyr, readr, devtools, rmarkdown, tibble
Computer Programs: RStudio, Microsoft Word, Microsoft Excel, Microsoft Powerpoint</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>