<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Brian G. Richards</title>
    <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Brian G. Richards</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://briangrichards.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Graduation</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/graduation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/graduation/</guid>
      <description>Another belated announcement! Back in July I defended my dissertation and in August I officially graduated. For any who are interested in the work that I have done, my dissertation is freely available from the University of Virginia library.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Transitioning to Blogdown</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/transitioning-to-blogdown/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/transitioning-to-blogdown/</guid>
      <description>I have felt for a while that this site needs a refresh. Previously, I had built it using Jekyll on a Windows machine. I’ve found that Jekyll was a pain to use in a Windows environment and that kept me from updating this site regularly. Fortunately, a few months ago I attended a RStudio webinar given by Yihui Xie on his new blogdown package.
Welcome to the new site created in blogdown!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Publications</title>
      <link>http://briangrichards.com/post/new-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Sep 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://briangrichards.com/post/new-publications/</guid>
      <description>I am pleased to (belatedly) announce a pair of publications!
The first is work that I did examining the line shapes of dipole-dipole interactions in a cold Rydberg gas.
The second is work done with Tao Zhou on the absence of collective decay in a cold Rydberg gas.
Both of these papers can be found at the links to the APS journal websites above.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>